#大家好 很多粉絲都說那個瓜瓜不知道哪裡去啦
Hi everyone! Many fans ask me the whereabouts of Gua Gua.
#我跟大家找一下 這瓜瓜
Let me search for him, search for Gua Gua.
#就在這附近一帶 我也不知道哪一個
He's in one of these cells, though I don't know exactly which.
#我看一下我就知道
But I can recognize him immediately.
#誒 這個是母的 肯定不是瓜瓜
Eh? This is female. It can't be Gua Gua.
#這是瓜瓜嗎
Is it Gua Gua?
#那麼瘦了
Is he that skinny now?
#不像啊
He shouldn't be.
#瓜瓜 你在哪裡誒 快點出來誒
Gua Gua? Where are you? Identify yourself!
#這個是母的
This is female.
#難道是這個
Or, this one?
#這個又不像 又好短哦 這個
It doesn't look like Gua Gua. It's too short.
#應該是這個 這個瘦了 這瓜瓜瘦了
It should be this one. This is skinny. Gua Gua is getting skinny.
#哇 這個就像瓜瓜啦 這個
Wa! This one looks like Gua Gua.
#現在都瘦啦 好長條的它
He's now so skinny, and long.
#現在這
You're now,
#瘦成這樣子啦 差點我都認不出你來啦
so skinny, that I can't even recognize you.
#好放下去 就是它
Put it back. Yea! This is Gua Gua.
#給它發了N個老婆 我都不知 我都記不清是多少個啦
I've given him uncountably many wives. I don't evne know, I can't even remember how many.
#它們過得很幸福
They're living together happily and merrily.
#相親相愛
They love and treasure each other.
#我們去看一下小胖 小胖在那里
Let's have a look at Small Fatty. Small Fatty is over there.
#現在跟大胖在一起了哦
He's now, living with Big Fatty.
#你看 這就是小胖
Look! This is Small Fatty.
#那個是大胖
And that is Big Fatty.
#小胖
Small Fatty!
#動都不敢動 全身僵硬
You're like a statue. Don't you dare to move?
#怎麼搞的
What's happened?
#別打架哦你們
Don't fight! Got it?
#你看 這個就是 大胖
Look! This is, Big Fatty.
#過來
Come to me!
#這個大胖 越養越瘦了
Big Fatty, is getting skinny now.
#沒辦法 它剛帶 帶完小孩
She took, took care of the babies. So that's why,
#現在都瘦了
that's why she's skinny.
#你看 大胖很重哦 大胖
Look! Big Fatty is really heavy, Big Fatty!
#小胖
Small Fatty!
#這個
This is...
小胖
Small Fatty!
#小胖
Small Fatty!?
Small Fatty?
#它在抓我
It scratches me.
#現在小胖比大胖還更重了
Small Fatty is even heavier than Big Fatty now.
#好啦 今天的視頻到這裡啦
Alright! The video ends here.
#我又要去煮飯了
I need to cook, again.